look at the 1820 stock volume, you can see it, I
think, in which you can
see stars up to 1280, so
buy ICICI GI also,
place a stock plus of 1232 and you can also take an option of 1260,
buy a stock plus of 24 here
for a target of 48,
okay, your skin is fabric, so here
its structure is very strong in the 1207 call
and today I am doing my 200 expansion
in the third convection session,
I welcome your convection call, good
afternoon ji, good afternoon, it is coming
out of the formation, its
short term moving average is rating above it,
it is trying to break its swing by making a log,
its
current price is
in this, brother's advice is our targets
of 327 and stop, okay,
you are picking Asian Paints right now,
but Rajesh Satpute ji had
picked it early in the morning, remember, the first deal was picked very well
when it opened and when we were in the initial
Okay, the singer is gathering, the train was
taken by Rajesh ji in the zone of around 3195 and
Rajesh ji till around 32, now this pick has been taken,
Amit ji tell me, at this time your
fresh conviction has called,
good afternoon,
see the structure of Asian Paint is definitely
strong, I believe that there is still a
lot of space here, today there is a press record,
so something new has to be given, so see,
Papa ji said absolutely right and Ashish ji should pay
some attention to FMC here, I think there will be
a contra play in the market, son, if the play is
here then my pick will be
Colgate Coolpad, if we talk about future then
Colgate is my pick at 1620, this is happening right now,
keep it at 16 plus and the target of trading
will be 1640 to 1650,
but there is strength and the resistance is
also formed around 1650, only one thing
I will add here, the day Colgate
starts trending above 1650, on that
day FMCG will easily go above 2000
Calls to buy are coming here too.